A funny story about a family... And the little girl who started it.
Curly Sue is a comedy, drama, family film directed by John Hughes.
Bill is a penniless drifter who scams strangers out of just enough money to feed
himself and his partner in crime, an orphan girl known as Curly Sue.
Bill and Curly Sue target Grey, a yuppie lawyer, but their con takes an unexpected
turn when the successful woman begins to like the ramshackle duo.
But there's one problem—Grey's jealous, conniving boyfriend, Walker.
Bill Dancer, played by Jim Belushi.
Curly Sue, played by Alisan Porter.
Grey Ellison, played by Kelly Lynch.
Walker McCormick, played by John Getz.
Tesio, played by Steve Carell.
Bernard Oxbar, played by Fred Thompson.
Curly Sue is a 1991 American comedy drama film written, produced, and directed by John Hughes, and
starring James Belushi, Kelly Lynch and Alisan Porter with Steve Carell in his film debut.
It tells the story of a homeless con artist and his young orphan
companion who gain shelter with a rich divorce lawyer.
This was the final film directed by Hughes before his death in 2009.
The film was released by Warner Bros.
on October 25, 1991 and received generally negative reviews from critics
while grossing $33.7 million against a $25 million budget.
The film explores themes of daughter, homeless person,
paternity, rich woman poor man, wealth.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.